eileenfisher.com 2018-11-17

# International Customers | EILEEN FISHER

**EILEEN FISHER PRIVACY POLICY**

_Last updated May 24, 2018_

This Privacy Policy describes and governs the information collection, use, and sharing practices of EILEEN FISHER, Inc. and its affiliates (for the purposes of this Privacy Policy, collectively "EILEEN FISHER", “we”, “us” or “our”). Our Privacy Policy reflects our long history of customer service and the high value we place on our customers' trust. EILEEN FISHER is committed to protecting our customers' right to privacy and to the ethical and responsible use of your information.

This Privacy Policy details the personal information we collect about you, the means through which we collect that information, with whom we share it, and how you can change your preferences regarding how we collect and use your information when you provide it to us. 

**What Information We Collect and How We Collect It**

We collect, store, and use information that you provide directly to us and information we acquire in other ways, as discussed below. Some of this information is personal information, meaning it relates to an identified or identifiable natural person. 

**Information We Acquire From You Directly**

We acquire information from you when you (a) provide information via any of the EILEEN FISHER Websites, (b) interact with any EILEEN FISHER checkouts, (c) participate in any EILEEN FISHER questionnaires, panels, contests, or sweepstakes, (d) communicate or interact with EILEEN FISHER customer service or (e) engage in any other electronic with EILEEN FISHER. Through these channels, you might provide us with information about you, information about the recipient of any merchandise you are ordering and/or having shipped, including, in either case, names, email addresses, postal addresses, phone numbers, genders, birthdays, marketing preferences, personal interests, credit card information, and other financial information. We also acquire other information about you when you interact with the EILEEN FISHER Websites and certain of its features, including accounts, checkouts, questionnaires, contests, sweepstakes and social media features. 

**Information We Acquire in Other Ways**

We, or our third party partners, may collect information through log files. This may include city and country location, IP address, browser type, device information, a unique identifier from your browser or device, and details of your usage such as your preferences (such as social media “pins”, “likes” and “dislikes”). We may also acquire information about you from third parties and publicly available information. Using this information helps us fulfill your orders, keep records, and provide products and services that may be of interest to you. 

**Technologies Used at EILEEN FISHER**

**Cookies:** A cookie is a simple file that is stored on your device by a website’s server. When you interact with EILEEN FISHER cookies and other similar technologies may be used for storing information, and accessing information stored on your device. 

These cookies and other similar technologies may include first party cookies (i.e., those placed by the website being visited) and third party cookies (i.e., those placed by a website other than the one being visited), Local Shared Objects (commonly referred to as “LSOs,” "Flash Cookies", or “HTML 5 Cookies”) and tracking pixels (including clear gifs). Cookies can either expire at the end of a session ("Session Cookies") or be persistent and last through multiple sessions ("Persistent Cookies"). Session Cookies can be helpful for remembering items you put in your shopping cart as you browse a website, or for security reasons. Persistent Cookies are stored on your device in between sessions, which allows for your preferences or actions to be remembered and used on a website or across different websites. Persistent Cookies may be helpful in remembering your preferences and choices when using a website or to ensure advertising messages are more relevant to you. 

Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. The "Help” function within your browser may tell you how to do this. Alternatively, you can visit www.allaboutcookies.org, which gives comprehensive information on how to disable cookies on a wide variety of desktop browsers. 

Please note that certain cookies are required for you to be able to take advantage of some of EILEEN FISHER’s important functions. If you disable or refuse cookies, some parts of our website may not function properly. Your web browser may let you choose your preference as to whether you want to allow websites to collect information over time about your online activities across different websites or online services. At this time, we do not respond to such "Do Not Track” or similar preferences you may have configured in your web browser, and we may continue to collect information in the manner described in this Policy. 

**Third Party Cookies:** We partner with advertising companies to place our advertising on other websites on the Internet. These companies may use third party cookies which allow them to develop personalized advertising so that it relates to information that may be of interest to you. 

**Web Beacons:** This is an electronic file on a web page that allows us to count and recognize users who have visited that page. Among other things, a web beacon can be used in HTML-formatted email to determine responses to our communications and measure their effectiveness - for instance, if you get an email from us and click on a link in that email to go to our website. You can generally avoid web beacons in email by turning off HTML display and displaying only the text portion of your email. 

**Geo-location:** Geo-location refers to technologies that permit us to determine your devices location. We may ask you to manually provide precise location information on our website, or to enable your mobile device to send us precise location information. We may also automatically use information from your web browser or computer to determine general location information, such as the city in which you live. 

**How We Use the Information We Collect**

By electing to enter into a contract with us for the purchase of goods, you allow us to use and retain your information as needed to provide you services, fulfill your order, administer and operate our loyalty program, comply with our legal obligations, and resolve disputes. 

These are also legitimate business reasons for the use and processing of your personal information. For example, we analyze transactional data for statistics that may contribute to the enhancement of our services. Another example would be if you place an order with us through one of our merchant suppliers, our merchant supplier may contact you if there is an issue with the order. 

**How We Share and Disclose Personal Information**

We do not sell your information to others and do not share your information other than as outlined in this Privacy Policy. However, there are certain situations where we may provide your information to third parties. These third parties are only authorized to use your information in order to provide you services and as otherwise outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

**Marketplaces and Partners Involved in Your Transaction:** Depending on how you interact with us, you may make purchases that involve third parties. For example, you may make a purchase that involves a third-party website or marketplace. In such situation, you may initially view products on an EILEEN FISHER website and are then directed to a third party website for purchase, and EILEEN FISHER facilitates the order. If this is the case, it may be clear to you that a third party is involved in your transaction. In these scenarios we may share your personal information with that third party. 

**Service Providers:** We may provide your personal information to certain service providers, in connection with the fulfillment of your purchase or the improvement of our products and services. These service providers may include delivery agents, email providers, customer support providers, customs brokers, technical support, international revenue authorities, and fraud management parties. 

**Third Party Marketing Features:** If you opt-in as described in the Section “Marketing, Promotional and Other Information", we may supply your personal information to third parties. If you use third party items that interact with the EILEEN FISHER websites, including social media features, blogs, or other applications or items, we may supply your personal information to those third parties. 

**EILEEN FISHER’s Protection:** We will disclose your personal information as required by law, when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, legal process, or to enforce our Terms & Conditions and other agreements. 

**Business Transitions:** In the event EILEEN FISHER goes through a business transition, such as a reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer, or other disposition of all or any portion of EILEEN FISHER’s business, assets, or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings) with or acquisition by another company, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred. 

**Your Consent:** We may share your information in other ways that you specifically consent to. 

**Other Disclosures:** We may disclose your Personal Information: (i) when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against persons or entities that may be causing injury to you, EILEEN FISHER, or others; (ii) when we believe that applicable law, legal process, or regulation requires it; or (iii) to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities or fraud. In some circumstances we may be required to provide your personal information to a law enforcement agency and prohibited from providing you notice of that event. 

**Aggregated Content:** We may also share aggregate information with our merchant partners, PR agencies, advertising agencies, and other third parties. By aggregate information we mean information from multiple users that is not personal information. 

**Securing and Retention of Personal Information:**

We take the security of your data very seriously. We take reasonable and appropriate measures to protect your data by using a variety of generally accepted standards, technologies, and processes. Please note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure and no one can guarantee absolute security. 

The security of your password is vital to the security of your data. We recommend that you do not share, reuse, or store any of your passwords with anyone else. 

We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. If you have questions regarding how long a specific type of information is retained, please contact us using the information below. 

**Marketing, Promotional and Other Information**

In certain cases, when interacting with EILEEN FISHER, you may be provided with a choice to opt-in or opt-out of receiving marketing and promotional information. In other non-marketing cases, you may not be presented this choice. If you, at any time, choose to opt-out of receiving such information, we will abide by that preference. Furthermore, at any time you may send us an email at [information@eileenfisher.com](mailto:information@eileenfisher.com) to opt out. You may also follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in the marketing communications you receive from EILEEN FISHER. In certain cases, we may give you the option to opt-in to receive marketing, promotional or other information from one of our partners or other third party. If you chose to opt-in for that, we will provide your personal information to that third party. 

No matter what your marketing preferences are, we may contact you to acknowledge, confirm, or fulfill any order that you place or for other legitimate business reasons. 

**Links to Other Websites**

The EILEEN FISHER Websites may include third-party advertising and links to third-party websites. We are not responsible for the content displayed or the practices of any such websites. We recommend that you review the privacy policy and terms and conditions of those websites. 

**Your Rights and Choices**

Some individuals have rights to request certain things of us regarding their personal information. If you would like to make a request to EILEEN FISHER regarding the personal information about you held by EILEEN FISHER, you may email us at [information@eileenfisher.com](mailto:information@eileenfisher.com) . We will respond to your requests regarding your personal information within 30 days. 

EILEEN FISHER adheres to applicable laws and regulations regarding your personal information moving across geographical and jurisdictional borders. 

Information submitted by you may be transferred by us to our other offices and/or to the third parties mentioned in the circumstances described above (see How We Use The Information We Collect), which may be situated (and may be processed by staff operating) in places other than your home jurisdiction, the U.S. and/or the European Economic Area (EEA). The countries concerned may not have similar data protection laws to your home jurisdiction, the US and the EEA. Where we transfer your information we will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy continues to be protected. By submitting information via the EILEEN FISHER website, you agree to this storing, processing, and transfer. 

**California Privacy Rights:** Residents of the State of California have the right to request from companies conducting business in California a list of all third-parties to which the company has disclosed certain personally identifiable information as defined under California law during the preceding year for third-party direct marketing purposes. 

**Children:** EILEEN FISHER does not provide products and services to children, or knowingly collect or solicit information from children under the age of 16. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 16 and believe he or she has disclosed personally information to us, please contact us at [information@eileenfisher.com](mailto:information@eileenfisher.com) . 

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, you can contact us by emailing us at [information@eileenfisher.com](mailto:information@eileenfisher.com) . You may also write to us at: 

Attn: **Vice President of Technology**  
EILEEN FISHER, Inc.   
2 Bridge Street, Suite 230  
Irvington, New York 10533

If we need, or are required, to contact you concerning any event that involves your information, we may do so by email, telephone, or mail.
